

Nguyen Duy Long Nhat

PYTHON DEVELOPER

30/01/2000

**** 0357791196

ICID Complex, Ha Dong, Ha Noi

Male

ndlongnhat@gmail.com

https://www.facebook.com/tra.vinh.16

SUMMARY

Currently, I am an electronics student who just graduated from PTIT academy. I have more than a year of experience as a deverloper. I feel very interested in a python developer and your company. Looking forward to cooperating with the company!

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING: Python, Dart, C++, HTML

LANGUAGE: Vietnamese, English

DATABASE : MySQL, PortgreSQL, MongoDB

VERSION CONTROL: Git, GitHub

EDUCATION

MAJOR: ELECTRONIC ENGINEERING POST AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

2018 - 2023 Form: Formal

WORK EXPERIENCE

POSITION: AI DEVELOPER (PYTHON) TINASOFT VIETNAM

February 2022 - August 2022 Description:

· Learn algorithms, write programs, and optimize runtime

· Process raw data and train AI models

CÔNG TY CỔ PHẦN TNHH HƯNG HÀ

POSITION: FLUTTER DEVELOPER

(DART)

October 2022 - October 2023

Description:

• Build UI, connect API and interaction processing when data is available

• View, check, merge code and build the app on the store

POSITION: INTERN PYTHON DEVELOPER WITHOUT SALARY

April 2024 - May 2024

CÔNG TY TNHH MỘT THÀNH VIÊN CÔNG NGHỆ VÀ TRUYỀN THÔNG 31

Description:

· Build python tools to craw data from website

· Build python tools to build and develop product, run product ads

POSITION: INTERN BACKEND PYTHON CÔNG TY TNHH AI COMPANY

DEVELOPER WITHOUT SALARY June 2024 - July 2024

Description:

- Build python tools to craw, get data from website and develop web product
- · Build MySQL databases, write and edit API with Flask, write Socket

PROJECTS

DESCRIPTION PROJECT: WEBSITE PROVIDING INFORMATION ABOUT **CRYPTO**

April 2022 - July 2022

COINR4 (PYTHON)

My responsibility:

- Recommend articles related to the article you are reading
- Recommend articles you may like
- · Optimize processing time

DESCRIPTION PROJECT:

APPLICATIONS FOR JOB SEARCHING CÔNG 365 (DART) AND TIMEKEEPING

October 2022 - October 2023

APP MOBILE ON STORE: CHAT365, TÌM VIỆC 365, CV 365, PC 365, CHẨM

My responsibility:

- Build new features (build UI, connect API, handle interface errors)
- · Handle errors arising from customers
- Optimize code and update applications on the store

ABOUT: BACK END, WEB APP, TOOL,

LOCAL APP

March 2024 - July 2024

PROJECT TO REVIEW (PYTHON)

*Back End:

Flask + PortgreSQL:

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/BackEnd_Vs_PortgreSQL

Flask + MySQL : https://github.com/SuperAdudu/BackEnd_Vs_MySQL Flask + MongoDB : https://github.com/SuperAdudu/BackEnd_Vs_MongoDB

*MicroService:

Hospital Management:

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/Hospital_Management_Using_MicroService

*Django:

Shop Online : https://github.com/SuperAdudu/Shop_Online_Django Real Time Chat : https://github.com/SuperAdudu/RealTime_Chat_Django CRM : https://github.com/SuperAdudu/CRM_App_Django

Basic Social Media:

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/Basic_Social_Media_Django

*Selenium:

Craw Shoppee Bot

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/Craw_Shoppee_Selenium

Multi Ad Facebook Bot:

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/Ads_Face_Selenium

Ad Zalo Bot

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/Ads_Zalo_Selenium

*Local App: https://github.com/SuperAdudu/Weather-App

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/ColorDetectionApp

https://github.com/SuperAdudu/ToDoListApp https://github.com/SuperAdudu/TranslatorApp